MUHAMAD NUR RIDWAN

Semarang, Jawa Tengah, Indonesia | Phone : <u>0895330823300</u> | E-mail : <u>muhamadnurridwan7@gmail.com</u> LinkedIn : <u>linkedin.com/in/muhamad-nur-ridwan-a1600a309</u> | Github : <u>https://github.com/Ridwan0126</u>

PROFILE

I am a 4th-semester student in the Informatics Engineering study program at Ngudi Waluyo University. I have an interest in Front-End but I can also do Back-End so it is possible for me to become Full-Stack. I am a highly motivated person, communicative, creative, adaptive, responsible, and open to new things. Have experience as a freelance Web developer for 1 year. In addition, previously I also attended the Full-Stack Web & Mobile Developer Bootcamp program at G2 Academy. would like to apply for the position of Front-End or Full-Stack Developer in a company or agency that applies technological advances, especially in application or website development.

EDUCATION

NGUDI WALUYO UNIVERSITY

2022 - PRESENT

4th year Informatics undergraduate student

GPA: 3.63 / 4.00

- I am a KIP K scholarship recipient at Ngudi Waluyo University.
- Participated in student exchange program at Semarang University.
- Faculty representative in the University Student Executive Board (BEM) in 2023.
- Participated in several leadership training sessions.
- Participated in a technology seminar.
- · Completed a website project.

COURSE

G2 ACADEMY SEPT 2021

Fullstack Mobile and Web Developer Bootcamp

Grade: B

- Learn React JS, React Native, and JAVA Programming.
- Website design using Figma.
- Creating final projects in the form of Front-end, Backend, and Fullstack.

ACHIEVEMENTS

INDONESIAN STUDENT DEBATE COMPETITION (KDMI)

JUNI 2024

I became an N1 judge

PEKSEMA BENGKULU UNIVERSITY

MEI 2024

Male solo song

PROGRAM PENGUATAN KAPASITAS ORMAWA (PPKO)

JUNI 2023

working together with village officials, residents and youth organizations to implement the climate village program.

PEKAN OLAHRAGA SENI KAMPUS (POSK)

SEPT 2022

Male solo song

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER 2023 - PRESENT

Freelance Web Developer

- Creating websites from the planning stage to maintenance.
- Collaboration with other campuses and study programs to create websites...

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

BEM NGUDI WALUYO UNIVERSITY

FEBRUARY 2023 - JANUARY 2024

Minister of Executive Secretary

- Passed funding in the KEMENDIKBUD PPKO program 2023
- Comparative study with other campuses
- Committee Chair for University Anniversary event

Information and Communication Division Staff

- Head of Secretariat Division in the committee of JATENG Technology Festival 2023
- Central Java regional working meeting of PERMIKOMNAS RI 2023
- Greater Semarang Regional Forum

BEM NGUDI WALUYO UNIVERSITY

SEPT 2022 - JANUARY 2023

Intern at the Ministry of Executive Secretary

- · Best Intern Staff of BEM Cakrawala Cabinet
- Participated in leadership and secretarial training sessions
- Assisted staff in improving their skills
- Became a committee member and ticket coordinator for the Campus Arts and Sports Week (POSK) event

COMITEE EXPERIENCE

FESTIVAL TEKNOLOGI JATENG 2023

SEPTEMBER 2023

Secretariat Coordinator

- University representative in the committee of the 2023 Central Java Technology Festival and oversees other universities in Semarang.
- Collaborate with secretary and PERMIKOMNAS JATENG to create administrative documents.
- Manage participant data and create links for registration, etc.

KONGKOW BARENG UNW

JUNI 2023

Committee Chair

- Achieve event visitor target of 500 people
- · Many high school students were interested in the campus
- · Received appreciation from residents and university leaders

PEKAN OLAHRAGA SENI DAN KAMPUS (POSK)

SEPTEMBER 2022

Events Division

- In charge of concert tickets and event promotion
- Responsible for Guest Star Accommodation

SKILLS

HARD SKILLS

- PHP
- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- SQL
- GitHub
- Figma

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Communication
- Collaboration
- · Problem Solving
- Creativity
- · Critical Thinking
- Attention to Detail
- Adaptability
- Fast Learner

PORTOFOLIO

YOU CAN SEE MY PORTFOLIO AND CERTIFICATES AT THE FOLLOWING LINK

Link: https://portofolio-muhamad-nur-ridwan.netlify.app/